I eat an entire pint of ice cream every
single day and still maintain a caloric
deficit. Here are some of the recipes I
made this week to stay fit and hit my
protein goal. This is what I call
brownie batter. You guys call it a rusty
pipe. Either way, it's insanely
delicious. This is peanut butter
halfbaked, peanut butter base with
brownies and cookie dough mixed in.
Absolute banger. This recipe will be out
in a couple days, so follow along to see
that. In continuation of my fall
seasonal treat series, this is pecan
pie. I don't even like pecan pie, but
this was banging. Oh my god. Tastes
exactly like a piece of pie. Then after
two plus years of testing, I perfected
my pistachio recipe. So I used it to
recreate Ben & Jerry's pistachio
pistachio flavor and it was genuinely as
good as some of the gelato I had when I
was in Italy. Then I did a tiramisu
flavor. This was Ben & Jerry's tiramisu.
Topped mascar pone flavored ice cream
with chocolate covered espresso beans
and shortbread pieces topped with some
chocolate sauce. And finally, I
perfected my mint chocolate chip recipe.
A mint flavored ice cream that doesn't
taste like toothpaste with a creamy
chocolate swirl that when mixed in
breaks up into perfect chocolate chips.